[{"answer": "Investments.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 5, "question": "What steps should I take right now to set myself up for financial success?", "qSentId": 4}, {"answer": "Suze Orman, dollars and cents, and the hottest issues of the day.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "How do I start preparing for my retirement?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "A DEFENSE\": You know, I'm not really opposed to anything in this situation.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "Ryan, why are you so opposed to gay people getting married?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "I'm in favor of having the citizens have the authority to go to the ballot box and vote about marriage.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Are you in favor of gay marriage?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "I'm in favor of marriage between a man and a woman.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "Are you in favor or against gay marriage?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "I don't think it's only that.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "That basically the reason a man and a woman should be allowed to marry rather than a man and a man or a woman and a woman, is to do with their ability to procreate?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "That's part of it.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "Is that part of it?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "So would you ban everyone over the age of 50 from getting married?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "The Supreme Court looked at these cases of the fundamental right to marry for prisoners and they understood again because of what marriage is, is a union of a man and a woman, prisoners have that same right partly because they come out of jail and they still have lives.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "Is your answer to that question yes?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "I feel compassion for you, and I'll tell you why.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "What it boils down to?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "The Constitution doesn't, which is why the Supreme Court shouldn't say that.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "Where does the American Constitution say that a same-sex couple can't get married?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "But don't want to have to obscure -- I think these are secondary issues.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "Do -- is that what you think is going to happen?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "So how do we strengthen the message that they shouldn't get divorced.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "And marriage is what connects the mother and the father with each other for the child.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "What if you were sterile and you couldn't have a child?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "-- we can have the government out of the marriage system.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "We're in the court of this public opinion, but in America, there are lots of people who agree with me.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "I'm 31.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "How old are you?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "It's -- I think at this point it is more of them than us, if you define us as main street, the people possibly in this room.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Is it more of them than us?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "I'm going to act like that's rhetorical because I don't know.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "So what's the interest rate of your student loans?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Well, now here we have the argument --", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Suze, what would you recommend?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Arguments over marriage.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "OK?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Is she?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "So that's why -- because -- do you feel -- and do you feel like you're OK?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "So do you have more than one piece of real estate?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Two, going to be three.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "How many do you have?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "On and off.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Are they really complicated, your taxes?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Years ago, I used to sit and I used to say to everybody, take Social Security at 62.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Fundamentally, is it getting older or younger now, the retirement age of most Americans?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "I love this for him.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "You have piece for Tiger Woods?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "I think that was a very, very large mistake.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "What do you make of that as a marketing ploy?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "Here's what you understand, if there was ever a time to go through bankruptcy, it is now.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "How do you recover from it?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Love it.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "What do you think about Cheryl Sandberg's new book \"Lean In\"?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "Hard working girl.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "But if it's a woman producer and she leaves your hotel room at 3:00 or 4:00 in the morning, what's everybody going to think?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "I love that.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "Another glass ceiling gets chipped away?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "Oh, so badly here, I can't even tell you.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "Do you want to get married, by the way?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "Well, you have to first teach them where are they going to get this money that they're going to save.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "And how would you suggest going about that?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Well, they have to earn it.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "Why are you giving them an allowance?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "I am trying.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "Are you saving money for you?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "Yes, Americans overspend.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "Do Americans overspend?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "That, you know, just seriously to live below your means but within your needs.", "docId": "130326pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "If I could get you to leave us with one overriding thought for all Americans tonight to think about money in a sensible way, what would you want it to be?", "qSentId": 699}]